http://tafkac.org/privacy-policy/

No comment yet
What information do we collect?
We collect information from you when you register on our site, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form.
When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.
What do we use your information for?
Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:
• To personalize your experience(your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs)
• To improve our website(we continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you)
• To improve customer service(your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs)
• To process transactionsYour information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
• To send periodic emailsThe email address you provide for order processing, will only be used
to send you information and updates pertaining to your order.If you decide to opt-in to our mailing list, you will receive emails that may include company news, updates, related product or service information, etc.
Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, simply click on the unsubscribe options at the bottom of every email..
How do we protect your information?
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or access your personal information.
We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.
After a transaction, your private information (credit cards, social security numbers, financials, etc.) will not be stored on our servers.
Do we use cookies?
Yes (Cookies are small files that a site or its service provider transfers to your computers hard drive through your Web browser (if you allow) that enables the sites or service providers systems to recognize your browser and capture and remember certain information
We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site traffic and site interaction so that we can offer better site experiences and tools in the future.
If you prefer, you can choose to have your computer warn you each time a cookie is being sent, or you can choose to turn off all cookies via your browser settings. Like most websites, if you turn your cookies off, some of our services may not function properly. However, you can still place orders over the telephone.
Do we disclose any information to outside parties?
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.
Third party links
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.
California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.
As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their control panel and going to the ‘Edit Profile’ page.
Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.
Online Privacy Policy Only
This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through our website and not to information collected offline.
Your Consent
By using our site, you consent to our websites privacy policy (obtained from Trustguard).
Changes to our Privacy Policy
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page.
This policy was last modified on July, 2010
Contacting Us
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.
admin (at) tafkac.org
Leave a Reply Cancle ReplyCommentName(required)
Email(required)
Website
Save my name, email, and website in this browser for the next time I comment.
Current ye@r *
Leave this field empty
Categories
Superstitions
Urban Legends
Most Popular Posts
Urban Legend (1998) Movie
25 Most Popular Urban Legends Still Being Told
Urban Legends - The 13th Floor
Real Life URBAN LEGEND:SLENDERMAN
Urban Legends - Open Casket Wedding
Urban Legends - Robert Johnson
Japanese Urban Legends
Urban Legends - Poltergeist Movie Curse
Badman's Top 10 - Creepy Urban Legends in Gaming (Feat. Jordan Underneath)
Urban Legends - The Rake
Recent Posts
Superstition As Persuasion
7 Halloween Superstitions You Don't Really Want to Believe
7 Celebrity Diet Secrets
Garlic: The Mystical Health Food
A History of Western Astrology
Greater Inflation Is An Extremely, Very Bad Concept
Superstition And Politics
ACLU Blasts NSA Surveillance With Video Featuring Creepy Santas
See Creepy Clip Of Dead Moth Being Inflated
The Crusdades: Urban Legends And Truth
Recent CommentsAnonymous on Superstitions of Players NBA Open CourtAnonymous on Superstitions of Players NBA Open CourtAnonymous on Superstitions of Players NBA Open CourtAnonymous on Superstitions of Players NBA Open CourtAnonymous on Superstitions of Players NBA Open CourtArchives
January 2015
February 2014
January 2014
December 2013
October 2013
September 2013
August 2013
© Urban Legends All Rights Reserved.
Theme zAlive by zenoven.
Privacy Policy
Contact
